关于在现代社会中如何处理卖淫问题，人们意见分歧。
Opinion is divided about what to do about prostitution in the modern world.
一些国家正在强化他们的法律，另一些国家则放松它们。
Some countries are toughening their laws, others relaxing them.
英国的法律在中间。
Britain's laws are somewhere in the middle.
英国在辩论法律，
As Britain debates its law,
德国人还有很多东西要学。
there's a lot to be learned from the Germans.
他们拥有世界上最自由的卖淫法律，
They have some of the most liberal prostitution laws in the world,
创造了欧洲最大的妓院，
which have created the biggest brothels in Europe,
大妓院。
the mega brothels.
有人说他们更好…
Some say they're better...
我觉得它们也很好，很特别，
I think they're something really nice and special, as well,
这里每个人都很开心。
and everyone is happy in here.
其他人认为他们更糟。
..others that they're worse.
有时候，我们真的疯了。
Sometimes, we have really insane
这里全是精神病人。
and totally mentally sick people here.
有一件事是肯定的——辩论变得相当激烈。
One thing's for certain - the debate's getting quite heated.
喊叫
SHOUTING
只有这样才能找出谁是对的，谁是错的—
There's only way to find out who's right and who's wrong -
付钱，通过门，
pay the money, pass through the doors,
进入天堂世界。
enter the world of Paradise.
英国人想卖淫合法化
The people in Britain who want to legalise prostitution
说它改善了妓女的条件。
say it improves conditions for prostitutes.
德国人合法化，12年前因为相同的原因。
The Germans legalised it for that very same reason 12 years ago.
但是当他们卖淫合法的时候，
But when they made prostitution legal,
他们也合法的妓院，不久之后，
they also legalised brothels and, soon after,
天堂般的地方诞生了。
places like Paradise were born.
他们称之为超级妓院。
They call it a mega brothel.
天堂连锁店有五家连锁店—
There are five in the Paradise chain -
而斯图加特的五层楼则是旗舰。
and the five-storey one in Stuttgart is the flagship.
150个女孩可以在晚上工作。
150 girls can work here in a night.
每年有50000名客户来访。
Up to 50,000 clients visit every year.
像沃尔夫冈这样的男人…
Men like Wolfgang...
这真是个天堂。
This is really a paradise
因为你有美丽的女孩。
because you have here beautiful girls.
我认识那些女孩
I know those girls
我不相信这些女孩的素质。
and I'm not convinced about the quality of the girls.
他们中的大多数我做了他妈的。
Most of them I did fuck.
翻译：
TRANSLATION:
这就是它的工作原理——男人付79欧元进来，
Here's how it works - the men pay 79 euros to come in,
穿上睡衣，
get a dressing gown,
吃点东西，
have a bite to eat,
喝一杯，
grab a drink,
挑女孩，
pick a girl,
上楼，
go upstairs,
得到钥匙，
get a key,
走进房间…
go into a room...
这就是乐趣开始的地方。
That's where the fun begins.
面试官：你睡过多少个女孩？
INTERVIEWER: How many girls have you slept with?
在这里，在500，我停止计数。
Here, at 500, I stopped counting.
对于那些认为为性付出代价的人，你会怎么说？…
What do you say to people who that think paying for sex is...
只是一件坏事？这事不应该做。
is just a bad thing? It shouldn't be done.
性是一种服务，是吗？
Sex is a service, yeah?
如果你想有良好的性生活，
If you want to have good sex,
你必须为这项服务付很多钱。
you must pay good money for this service.
这对女孩本身有什么影响？，
What effect does that have on the girls themselves,
有这么多的性？
having all this sex?
我不知道。我从未想过…
I don't know. I never thought about...
这是我的避孕套部分。
Here's my...my condom part.
你在里面有多少避孕套？
How many condoms have you got in there?
老实说，我不算他们。我够了。
To be honest, I don't count them. I have enough.
比你所需要的更多？对.也许30, 50。真的.
More than you could ever need? Yes. Maybe 30, 50. Wow.
我得说，不是每个人都在洗澡，
I have to say, not everyone is taking a shower,
客户的。有些男人不洗澡
of the clients. Some guys don't take a shower
我有我的婴儿纸，我把它们清洗干净。
and I have my baby paper and I clean them.
即使他们洗了个澡，也没关系。
Even if they took a shower, it doesn't matter.
我也清洗它们。我还有些什么？
I clean them too. What else do I have here?
当然，振动器！
Of course, a vibrator!
都笑了
BOTH LAUGH
我有一个小的。
I have a small one
因为有些男人有时候会有点咄咄逼人。
because some men sometimes can be a little bit too aggressive
也许太粗糙了，所以小的很好。
and too rough, maybe, so a small one is good.
我的最后一件事，对我来说也很重要，
My last thing that is also, for me, very important,
是硅胶。像麻醉剂一样。
it's silica gel. It's something like an anaesthetic.
你可以在阴道使用它。
You can use it at the vagina.
它..
It's...
你一点感觉也没有了，
You don't feel anything any more,
所以有时候，当我有很大的疼痛时，我会使用它。
so sometimes, when I have big pain, I use it.
这就像是一个小保险
It's something like a small insurance
如果疼痛变得太大。
if the pain is getting too big.
我的包里有两个。
I have two of it in my bag.
23岁的乔茜已经在这个行业工作
At 23, Josie has already been working in this business
四年了。她来到了超级妓院
for four years. She's come to the mega brothel
因为她听说这是赚大钱的地方。
because she's heard it's the place to make big money.
天堂是德国最著名的高档妓院之一。
Paradise is one of the most famous high-end brothels in Germany.
它在客户中有特殊的引诱方式，
It has a special approach to luring in clients,
作为“男人健康”的水疗中心—
presenting itself as a spa for the "wellness of a man" -
提供桑拿、蒸汽房和自助餐，
offering sauna, steam room and buffet,
只要一点点性爱就可以了。
with just a little sex on the side.
这个策略是虚构的大妓院的老板，Jurgen Rudloff。
That ruse was dreamed up by the mega brothel's owner, Jurgen Rudloff.
但如果他们试图触摸我的阴道或乳房，我说，“停止，
but if they try to touch my vagina, or the breast, I say, "Stop,
“这不是免费的，在这里。”
"that's nothing for free, here."
因为那不是…
Because that's not...
是的我们是妓女，不是荡妇。
Yeah - we are prostitutes, not sluts.
你知道吗？这是一个很大的不同！
You know?! That's a big difference!
乔茜在它的厚。
Josie's in the thick of it.
有一次我做爱30分钟。
With one I had sex 30 minutes.
没关系，我们戴上避孕套，现在做爱了。
It was OK - we put the condom on, we had sex now.
所以，没有前戏，你知道吗？那是非常困难的，
So, there was no foreplay, you know? That was very difficult,
你认为，”Jesus，
and you think, "Jesus,
“谁的阴道能存活下来？”
"how does anyone's vagina survive that?"
而我的另一个客户，他想要半个小时的口交。
And the other client I had, he wanted a half-hour oral sex.
如果你半小时口交，这里一切都很痛，
If you give half-hour oral sex, here, everything is hurting,
感觉你再也不能动它了，对吗？。
and it feels like you can't move it any more, correctly.
这也是非常累人的。
It's also very exhausting.
听起来可能不太愉快—
It may not sound too pleasant -
但这算是女孩子们的好夜晚。
but this counts as a good night for the girls.
如果你不做爱，你就不会赚钱。
If you're not having sex, you're not earning money.
乔茜的作品，直到晚上四时关闭，妓院。
Josie works until four that night, when the brothel closes.
第二天早上她就起床了，
And she's up first thing the next morning,
11开门时准备好。
to be ready when the doors open at 11.
为期两周的民间节日是她把钱耙进去的好机会。
The fortnight-long folk festival is her opportunity to rake it in.
如果你不介意我问你，
If you don't mind me asking,
那么你一天有多少客户？
so how many clients do you have normally, in a day?
在周末，它可能是15，在非常非常好的一天，20？
At the weekend, it can be maybe 15 and in a very, very good day, 20?
但那是非常非常非常好的一天！
But that's a very, very, very good day!
对我来说，这样做是很正常的，因为我现在这么做了。
For me it is quite normal doing that because I do that now for so
很多次，这么长时间，我真的不再去想它了。
many times, for so long time and I don't really think about it any more.
在我从事这项工作之前，我在麦当劳工作。
Before I worked at that business, I was working at McDonald's
这是我卖巨无霸，双层麦当劳
and it was normal for me to sell the Big Mac, McDouble
和芝士汉堡，现在对我来说是很正常的。
and Cheeseburger and nowadays it is for me very normal.
一天击中她20个男人的目标，
To hit her target of 20 men a day,
乔茜将要工作12个小时。
Josie will have to work for 12 hours.
至少通勤时间很短。
At least it's a short commute.
一楼的俱乐部，闻起来像是性…
The club on the first floor, it smells like sex...
也许像防腐剂和精子。
Maybe like preservative and sperm.
好像女孩们不够努力，天堂让她们付出代价。
As if the girls didn't have it hard enough, Paradise makes them pay
和男子入场费一样。
the same as the men's entrance fee
为了在里面工作的特权。
for the privilege of working inside.
政府每天给他们征收25欧元的定额税率—
And the government taxes them a flat rate of 25 euros a day -
他们赚什么。
whatever they earn.
以一张床的价格为准，
On top of the price of a bed,
这意味着大多数女孩每天都要减少127欧元。
that means most girls start every day down 127 euros.
祝你今天愉快!
Have a nice day!
谢谢您!你太。
Thank you! You too.
但大妓院的老板Jurgen Rudloff坚称他不是
But the mega brothel's owner Jurgen Rudloff insists that he's not
剥削女孩。
exploiting the girls.
听起来可能有点荒唐，
It may sound absurd,
但是尤尔根对天堂是一家家族企业很认真。
but Jurgen is serious about Paradise being a family business.
他让大儿子来经营桑拿，他甚至还经营。
He got his eldest son to manage the sauna - and he even
带着他十几岁的女儿和他一起去大妓院。
brings his teenage daughter into the mega brothel with him.
你觉得你爸爸的生意怎么样？
What do you think about your daddy's business?
我真的真的为我爸爸感到骄傲。
I'm really, really proud of my dad
我总是站在他身后。
and I'm always standing behind him.
真是太好了。
It's something really nice.
这是不同的和特殊的，以及每个人都很高兴。
It's something different and special as well and everyone is happy.
当我和我的朋友和英国朋友交谈时，
When I talk to my friends and British friends,
他们都退后了一步，觉得很奇怪。
they are all taking a step back and they find it quite weird that
人们喜欢这份工作，
people like this job,
人们做那份工作，
that people do that job,
因为他们发现人们裸体走路很奇怪，是的，
because they find it weird that people walk around naked and, yeah,
这和我的想法不同。
it's different to my thinking.
我想以后在这里工作。
I would love to work here later on.
但在管理方面。不是工人吗？
But in the management side. Not as a worker?
不，我不这样认为，我宁愿选择管理层。
No, I don't think so, I would rather take the management side
而不是工人一边。
and not the worker side.
那是为什么？
Why is that?
这是个难回答的问题。
That's a hard question.
我不知道，这只是我爸爸的方式，
I don't know, it's just the way of my dad,
我只是想像我爸爸一样，
I just want to be like my dad and, well,
我对女人做她们做的事没有问题。
I don't have a problem with women doing that what they do.
我真的没有这个问题，
I really don't have a problem with that,
但这不是我拥有未来的方式。
but it's not my way of having my future.
但并不是所有的女孩都希望将来卖淫。
But it's not as if all the girls want a future in prostitution either.
客户之间的，
Between clients,
乔茜偷偷回到楼上去追求她真正的野心。
Josie sneaks back upstairs to pursue her real ambition.
我今天在做作业。
I'm doing my homework today.
德国的政治。
It's politics in Germany.
也许政治并不是妓女所谈论的。
Maybe politics is not what a prostitute is talking about
当她和其他女人在俱乐部聊天的时候。
when she's chatting in the club with other women.
通常，当我对别人说，
Normally, when I say to other people,
我现在需要时间，我得做家庭作业，
I need time for myself now, I have to do my homework,
每个人都在看着你，“你在干什么？”
everyone is looking at you like, "What are you doing?"
这就像，你在妓院找金但…我的目标是
It's like, you're looking for gold in a bordello but... My aim is that
我可以学习一天，我想学习犯罪学。
I can study one day and I would like to study criminology.
它对我有个人的意义和个人的联系。
It has a personal meaning and a personal connection for me
因为这里是红灯和红灯。
because here in the red light business and the red light
区，你会看到很多犯罪和皮条客和给钱的妇女。
district, you see a lot of crime and pimps and giving the money to women.
我不得不看到很多暴力行为。
I had to see a lot of violence.
如果我能学犯罪学，那对我来说是件私事。
It would be a personal thing for me if I could study criminology.
这就是为什么我必须非常雄心勃勃，因为你需要一个良好的证书。
That's why I have to be very ambitious, because you need a good certificate for it.
乔茜不是唯一一个想大。
And Josie's not the only one thinking big.
萨尔布吕肯正在建造的新乐园将是第六个。
The new Paradise being built in Saarbrucken will be the sixth
连锁大妓院…如果他们能及时打开。
mega brothel in the chain... if they can get it open in time.
随着越来越多的国家使卖淫成为非法行为，德国正在成为现实。
As more countries make prostitution illegal, Germany is becoming
欧洲性旅游者选择的目的地。
the destination of choice for sex tourists in Europe.
这有助于推动性交易的价值。
That's helped to drive the value of the sex trade to
180亿欧元——是英国价值的三倍。
18 billion euros - three times its worth in Britain.
有这么多钱，
With so much money at stake,
难怪天堂的管理有点神经兮兮的。
no wonder Paradise's management are a little jumpy.
很明显，萨尔布吕肯项目对企业至关重要。
It's clear that the Saarbrucken project is vital for the business.
300英里外的斯图加特，
300 miles away in Stuttgart,
随着民间节日的全面展开，应该是他们最忙的时候了。
with the folk festival in full swing it should be their busiest time.
相反，客户比以往任何时候都少—
Instead there are fewer clients than ever -
女孩们的利润正在遭受折磨。
and the girls' profits are suffering.
你好.
Hi.
今天发生了什么？，
What happened today,
如果我能用一个词来概括它，
if I could summarise it in one word,
我会说，没有！
I would say, nothing!
真让我失望。
I'm very disappointed.
我赚了250英镑，但你得把账算在内，
I made 250, but you have to count the entry away,
所以只剩下100个。
so just 100 left.
那是…
That's a...
该死的一天。
a shit day.
我找不到比这更礼貌的词了。
I can't find a better word for it that is more polite.
真是糟糕的一天，我在工作十三
It's really a shit day and I'm working thirteen
现在半小时了。
and a half hours now.
所以今天真是糟糕的一天。
So today is just a bad day.
为什么所有的俱乐部都过得很艰难？
Why are all the clubs having a tough time?
我想俱乐部太多了。
I guess there are just too many clubs.
在每一个…
In every...
在大多数村庄里也有一个小俱乐部。
In most of the villages there's also a small club.
你知道，那太过分了。
You know, that's just too much.
俱乐部应该少一些。
There should be less clubs
然后这些家伙会更挤到俱乐部去。
and then the guys would come more crowded to the clubs.
我将在楼下做最后一轮。
I will make a last round downstairs.
也许有人想要，如果不是，我就去睡觉。
Maybe somebody wants and if not I will go to sleep.
因为合法化，一些估计女生人数
Since legalisation, some estimate the number of girls
在德国工作已经翻了一番。
working in Germany has doubled.
现在有400000个，
There are now 400,000 of them,
英国工作人数的五倍。
five times the number working in Britain.
大多数是从最贫困的国家来的移民。
Most are immigrants who have travelled from the most deprived
欧洲联盟国家，如罗马尼亚和保加利亚。
countries of the European Union, like Romania and Bulgaria.
费利西亚是他们中的一员。
Felicia's one of them.
她已经在俱乐部工作七个月了。
She's been working in the club for seven months now
它开始接近她了。
and it's starting to get to her.
但贫穷并不是女孩的唯一原因。
But poverty isn't the only reason girls
走进卖淫界。
enter the world of prostitution.
德国政府估计这个国家有90%的妓女。
The German government estimates 90% of prostitutes in the country
被迫从事性交易的皮条客。
are forced to work in the sex trade by pimps.
最脆弱的女孩是那些已经
The most vulnerable girls are those who've already
经历性剥削，
experienced sexual exploitation,
像乔茜，谁在遭受别人接近她的手。
like Josie, who suffered at the hands of someone close to her.
那是我10, 11岁的时候。
It was when I was 10, 11.
我想我可以说他是个魔鬼。
I guess I could say he was the devil in person.
他殴打我，还做了一些性侵犯。
He was beating me and he also did some sexual abuse.
这条线过得很不好，我想在那之后，
The line was crossed in a very bad way and I guess after that,
你的一部分正在死去
a part of you is dying a little bit
做妓女也没什么大不了的。
and it's not a big deal any more to work as a prostitute.
我认识的大多数女孩都是隐私，
Most of the girls I got to know in privacy,
他们也有很多不好的经历。
they had also a lot of bad experiences
在他们的童年或过去。
in their childhood or in the past.
暴力的男人或他们母亲的暴力前男友
Violent men or a violent ex-boyfriend of their mother
或者他们也曾性虐待的童年。
or they had also sexual abuse in their childhoods.
许多有这种命运的女人最终成为卖淫者。
A lot of women with that destiny end in up the prostitution.
不可能假装卖淫不是一件丑陋的事。
There's no pretending prostitution isn't an ugly business.
它使少数人毫发无损。
It leaves few people unscathed.
自从米迦勒开始在天堂工作，他的关系
Since Michael started working in Paradise, his relationship
他的妻子——他童年的情人——已经崩溃了。
with his wife - his childhood sweetheart - has fallen apart.
他的工作，至少，似乎进展顺利。
His work, at least, seems to be going well.
反对赔率，
Against the odds,
萨尔布吕肯新乐园随时准备开门迎客。
the new Paradise in Saarbrucken is ready to open its doors on time.
今天应该是值得庆祝的一天。
It should be a day to celebrate.
但当党内开始时，一大群记者
But while the party's starting inside, a horde of press
抗议者包围了大门。
and protesters have laid siege to the gates.
他们的主要指控之一是大型妓院。
One of their main allegations is that the mega-brothels
强迫卖淫的好处。
benefit from forced prostitution.
这些女人并不孤单。突然，一群好战分子，
And these women are not alone. Suddenly, a group of militant,
国际女权主义者加入了这场斗争。
international feminists joined the fight.
抗议者认为大型妓院提供了
The protesters believe the mega-brothels provide
强迫卖淫的完美封面。
the perfect cover for forced prostitution to happen.
当然，妓院里也有强迫卖淫。
Of course there is forced prostitution also in these brothels.
有观察男人在前面开车的女人。
There are observations of men who drive women in front of the place.
女人出来后，把钱交给男人
Women come out later, give their money to the men
他们开走了。
and they drive away.
我认为阻力越来越大。
I think the resistance is becoming stronger.
妓院老板可以负刑事责任。
A brothel owner can be held criminally responsible
如果强迫卖淫发生在他的前提下。
if forced prostitution occurs on his premises.
但批评者说这只是使案件合法化
But critics of legalisation say it's only made cases
强迫卖淫更难证明。
of forced prostitution harder to prove.
现代皮条客和毒贩用精妙的技术
Modern pimps and traffickers use an incredibly subtle technique
控制女孩。
of controlling girls.
这就是我的爱人的方法。
It's called the Loverboy method.
皮条客冒充女孩的男朋友
The pimps pretend to be the girls' boyfriends
在鼓励他们成为妓女之前。
before encouraging them to become prostitutes.
一个经历过的女孩是塔蒂亚娜，
One girl who has been through it is Tatiana,
费利西亚俱乐部里最好的朋友。
Felicia's best friend from the club.
此刻，我有了我的家人。
At the moment, I have my family.
我不是只为我工作。
I am not working only for me.
在罗马尼亚我没有好的…
In Romania I don't have a good...
现状。
..situation.
你是怎么进入这个行业的？
How did you get into the business?
我遇到了一些…
I met some...
某人
someone
他假装他爱上了我
and he was pretending that he was in love with me
然后他问我是否想做这份工作。
and then he asked me if I want to do this job.
刚开始，
At the beginning,
我说：“完全没有。你疯了吗？”
I said, "Completely no. Are you crazy?
“我不想这样做。我的生活从来没有过。”
"I don't want to do this. Never ever in my life."
但我在想我要做什么
But I was thinking about what I'm going to do
如果我每次都说不，他会送我回家。
if I say every time no, he would send me back home.
你第一次做这项工作是在德国吗？
So the first you did the job was here in Germany?
是的，它在德国。
Yes, it was here in Germany.
你能告诉我第一次的故事吗？
Can you tell me the story about that first time?
啊，天哪！这是可怕的
Oh, my God! It was horrible
现在很好笑。
and now it's funny.
他喝醉了，
He was drunk,
又老又不干净
old and not so clean
他每次放屁。
and he fart every time.
我的男朋友…
My "boyfriend"...
说我必须为我们赚钱。
..said that I must make money for us.
那全是谎话，因为钱只给他。
That was all a lie because the money was only for him.
他有工作吗？
Did he have a job?
不，他的工作是对我撒谎。那是他的工作。
No, his job was to lie to me. That was his job.
帕拉代斯的许多女孩都讲同样的故事。
Many girls in Paradise tell the same story.
我的爱人是最有效的方法
The Loverboy method is most effective
用在非常年轻的女孩身上。
when used on very young girls.
虽然立法开始充满善意，
Although legalisation started out full of good intentions,
最后，这没多大区别。
in the end, it's made little difference
为了女孩们的生活。
to the lives of the girls.
对于许多女孩来说，天堂的世界是难以逃避的。
For many girls, the world of Paradise is hard to escape.
不是乔茜。
Not for Josie.
你知道，在某些方面，
You know, in some ways,
在俱乐部待这么久感觉像一个监狱。
it feels like a prison to stay so long in a club.
你就呆在那里，工作，睡觉，工作和睡觉。
You just stay there, work, sleep, work and sleep
再说一遍，你知道，每天，在这中间，你吃东西。
and again, you know, every day and, in-between, you eat.
她仅仅三周就在回家的路上了。
She's on her way home after only three weeks.
民俗节日未能兑现她所希望的利润。
The folk festival failed to deliver the profits she hoped for.
但尽管乔茜继续她的研究，
But although Josie's continuing her studies,
她还在计划找一家新妓院来工作。
she's still planning to find a new brothel to work in.
性工作者的生活是很难留下的。
The life of a sex worker is hard to leave behind.
男人：当你在谈论你未来的计划时…是吗？
MAN: When you're talking about your plans for the future... Yeah?
那一个不涉及性的事业呢？哦!
..what about a career that doesn't involve sex? Oh!
嗯...哦，当然，我可以想象得到，但是，呃…
Um... Oh, of course, I could imagine that, but, er...
呃，很难…
It's, er, very difficult to...
寻找，呃…让我们说去找
to find the, er... let's just say to find
连接到正常工作，正常人，普通朋友。
a connection back to a normal job, to normal people, normal friends.
我不再有普通朋友了，只是很少。
I don't have normal friends any more, just very less.
这些都是我三年前的朋友，你知道吗？
And these are just the friends I had three years ago also, you know?
呃，我还没有认识新的“正常”朋友
I haven't, er, got to know new "normal" friends
谁不做性交易？。
who are not in the sex business.
我可以告诉你，我也在博览会上，
I can show you, I was at the fair too,
和民间节日，我赢得了一些东西。
and the folk festival and I won something.
我的“我爱你”熊，我的泰迪熊。
My "I love you" bear, my teddy bear.
它在床上最好的地方，在我旁边！
It gets the best place in the bed, next to me!
你的私人生活中有多少男人？哦，只有16。
How many men have you had in your normal, personal life? Oh, just 16.
1…6。别换了，是60！16！她笑着说
1...6. Don't change it was 60! 16! SHE LAUGHS
你睡了多少客户？哦...
And how many clients have you slept with? Oh...
我不那么肯定，当我这么说的时候，
I'm not so sure, when I say that,
如果这对我的……对我的未来有好处，说实话！
if it's so good for my...for my planned future, to be honest!
她笑着说
SHE LAUGHS
嗯，很多，真的很多。
Um, a lot, really a lot.
不…我猜最坏的男婊子
Not... I guess the worst male whore
没有那么多……很多男人或女人。给我们号码。
doesn't have so much...much men or women. Give us the number.
我猜大概是15000点左右吧？
I guess it's around 15,000, maybe?
不，呃…！是的，我想大概是15000点左右。
No, er...! Yeah, it is like around something like 15,000, I think.
什么…？是啊!现在，当我说出来的时候，我感到很难过！
What...? Yeah! Now, when I say it, I feel so sad!
我真的不知道为什么！但是，呃…为什么？这么多客户！
I don't really know why! But, er... Why? So many clients!
她咯咯地笑
SHE GIGGLES
我不知道。
I don't know.
乔茜是幸运的，她可以去天堂。
Josie's lucky that she could get out of Paradise.
八个月后，费利西亚仍在斯图加特的旗舰俱乐部。
Felicia's still in the flagship club in Stuttgart after eight months.
但业务缓慢意味着
But the slow business means
她几乎没有攒多少钱。
she's hardly saved more than she started with.
300英里外，在萨尔布吕肯的新俱乐部，
300 miles away, in the new club in Saarbrucken,
他们也遇到类似的问题。
they're suffering similar problems.
来自法国的新客户的承诺未能兑现。
The promise of new clients from France has failed to deliver.
巨型妓院不拔的足够的赌客
The mega brothel's not pulling in enough punters
米迦勒感到压力。
and Michael's feeling the pressure.
更糟糕的是，今天是他的生日。
Worse still, today is his birthday.
与妻子疏远，
Estranged from his wife,
他吃饭的唯一合作伙伴是来自俱乐部的酒保。
his only partner for dinner is the barman from the club.
米迦勒做这项工作已经八年了。
Michael's been doing this job for eight years now
生日是思考他的未来的好时机。
and a birthday is a good time to reflect on his future.
笛声
SIREN WAILS
那些未来的计划就要被怀疑了。
Those plans for the future are about to be thrown into doubt.
这是德国历史上最大的一次妓院连锁活动。
It's the biggest raid on a brothel chain in German history.
尤尔根所有的大型妓院都被抢劫了，
All of Jurgen's mega brothels are raided,
米迦勒是被捕的五人之一。
and Michael is one of the five people arrested.
留下来的姑娘们被卷入了抢劫，
The girls who stayed behind are caught up in the raid,
就像塔蒂亚娜，费利西亚最好的朋友。
like Tatiana, Felicia's best friend.
我听说了，“警察，举起手来，没有人动，没有人动。”！
I hear about, "Police, hands up, nobody move, nobody move!
“坐在那里，坐在那里！”我就像，“哇！这是个玩笑吗？！”
"Sit there, sit there!", and I was like, "Whoa! Is this a joke?!"
因为如果是个玩笑，我就害怕得像地狱一样。
Cos, if it is a joke, I was scared as hell.
我从没见过这么多警察
I never seen, in my life, so much police
而且，每一分钟，越来越多的警察来了。
and, every minute, come more and more and more police.
我们整个门都开着，太冷了。
Our whole doors was open and it was so cold.
我赤身裸体，你知道吗？。我在工作。
I was naked, you know. I was on a job.
他们问我：“21岁以下的人是谁？”
And they asked me, "Who's under 21?"
我起来了。他们告诉我必须打扮我，拿我的东西，
I was up. They told me that I must dress me up, take my stuff,
因为我们必须去警察局。
because we must go to the police station.
是的，我在那里呆了好几个小时。
And, yeah, I stayed there for hours.
他们问了我很多问题。
They asked me a lot of questions.
我是如何开始这项工作的，他们想要很多细节，很多。
How I started this job, they wanted a lot of details, a lot of them.
21岁以下的最易受伤害的妓女，
The most vulnerable prostitutes, who are under 21,
为收集证据而受到警方的讯问
are questioned by the police in a bid to gather evidence
帕拉代斯的女孩被迫卖淫。
that girls in Paradise have been forced into prostitution.
如果是这样的话，米迦勒和尤尔根可能面临刑事指控。
If so, Michael and Jurgen could face criminal charges.
现在，这是米迦勒的新家—
For now, this is Michael's new home -
在斯图加特郊区的一个监狱候审。
a remand prison on the outskirts of Stuttgart.
尤尔根尚未被捕，有待进一步调查。
Jurgen has not been arrested yet, pending further investigations.
但尽管突袭
But despite the raid
逮捕了几名管理人员，
and the arrest of several members of the management,
大妓院本身并没有关闭。
the mega brothel itself has not closed.
今天晚上还有客人要来。
There are still clients turning up this very night.
它只是表明，无论发生在天堂—
It just goes to show that, whatever happens in Paradise -
或者其他妓院—
or other brothels like it -
卖淫合法化的德国人在这里停留。
legalised prostitution for the Germans is here to stay.
他们的经验应该站在辩论的最前线。
Their experience should be at the forefront of the debate
对英国来说什么是对的。
over what's right for Britain.
红蜂传媒有限公司字幕
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd